socialtrade.biz 2016-07-04

# Social Trade | Part time Work | Online Work at home

www.socialtrade.biz is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and members. The Social Trade team members are members themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you.

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission. 

If you have registered as a member we may occasionally update you on services, news and special offers via e- mail, post & telephone. You will be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you become a member of Social Trade.

All Social Trade members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by using the "Unsubscribe" link in the email communication sent to you.

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of members as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Social Trade uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us.

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:   
In the event that Social Trade sells or buys any business or assets.  
if Social Trade or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets.  
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Social Trade, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to Social Trade you may do so by contacting us. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information.
